<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:html="http://www.w3.org/TR/REC-html40" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
<channel>
<title>Creation: Latest Articles by Leigh Scott (RSS)</title>
<link>https://creation.trovster.com</link>
<description>Creation: Latest Articles by Leigh Scott (RSS)</description>
<link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="/" />
<link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="/company/leigh-scott/rss/" />
<language>en</language>
<ttl>300</ttl>
	<item>
		<title>A Useful Link</title>
		<link>/news/2007/06/27/a-useful-link/</link>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Whilst looking through the <a href="http://www.businesslink.gov.uk">Business Link West Midlands website</a> I wondered how
many of you have spoken to Business Link and taken advantage of what they have to offer. </p>

<p>The site itself is crammed with useful information and details of what help is available. The section on <a
href="http://www.businesslink.gov.uk/bdotg/action/layer?r.l1=1073858790&amp;topicId=1073866776&amp;site=131&amp;r.s=tl">grants</a>
is particularly interesting as you can enter a few details to see what funding is there for you to apply for. Give them a
call, and see how they can help you. We&#8217;ve dealt with many people from Business Link and I can honestly say they are
always very helpful and professional. Many of our clients have benefited and received grants towards websites, design work
and other consultancy fees. The most recent of which is <a href="/portfolio/websites/instant-training-website/">Instant
Training</a> based in Telford, who have just seen their gorgeous new site go live.</p>

<p>To make it easier for you, <a href="/">Creation</a> are on the approved list of Business Link Consultants and have been
for a number of years. This means, if you ask us to do the work, you can claim any grant assistance available to you.
Sometimes this can be up to 50% towards the cost of a new website, for example. </p>

<p>Find your <a href="http://www.businesslink.gov.uk">local Business Link branch</a> and call them to see what&#8217;s
available to you. If I can be of any help, just let me know and I will point you in the right direction.</p>
]]></description>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2007 13:46:51 +0100</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="true">/news/2007/06/27/a-useful-link/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Leigh Scott</dc:creator>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>In Partnership with Xerox Global Services</title>
		<link>/news/2007/05/28/in-partnership-with-xerox-global-services/</link>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Last year we were chosen as a new design partner for Xerox Global Services, the division of Xerox responsible for offering
on-site services for a large number of big companies and organisations nationwide.</p>

<p>Since our introduction to the various sites we have completed a number of projects with successful results. All our
services, including the fixed price packages and solutions listed in our services section, are available to all sites and
all Xerox customers. There are some services available you may not be aware of, in fact, we may not be aware of them yet!
Remember, if you have a design, web or print problem to solve just ask. We&#8217;ve been able to help already on a number of
occasions with excellent results.</p>

<p>We look forward to building a stronger relationship with Xerox and their customers and providing the very best in design
for print and web.</p>

<p>If you need any further help or advice on our partnership and what we can do for you, contact me <a
href="mailto:leigh@creation.uk.com">leigh@creation.uk.com</a>, your print room manager or Xerox representative.</p>
]]></description>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2007 15:40:09 +0100</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="true">/news/2007/05/28/in-partnership-with-xerox-global-services/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Leigh Scott</dc:creator>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Donate Unwanted PCs</title>
		<link>/news/2007/05/20/donate-unwanted-pcs/</link>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Help students in The Gambia with your unwanted PCs. Following a visit to the region by our good friends at <a
href="http://www.tlc.ac.uk">Tamworth &amp; Lichfield College</a>, John Fontaine and Belinda Ball, we are trying to help them
collect computer equipment for students to use in Gambia.</p>

<p>This part of the world is very poor but everyone is keen to learn. The students have very limited facilities at present
and in some cases are using very old manual typewriters to learn keyboard skills. So our unwanted PCs would be a distinct
step up for them.</p>

<p>John and a friend of the College have made arrangements to ship any working PCs, capable of running Windows 2000, to the
College in The Gambia. A container will be packed up and sent over when it&#8217;s full. <a
href="mailto:leigh@creation.uk.com">Let me know</a> if you have any PCs you would like to donate.</p>

<p>You could also be saving money by helping out, now the Regulations implementing the <a
href="http://www.netregs.gov.uk/netregs/legislation/380525/473094/?lang=_e">WEEE Directive</a> (Waste Electrical and
Electronic Equipment) in the UK were entered into force on 2nd January 2007. A directive to promote recycling and reduce
waste. Find out more about the WEEE Directive and <a href="http://weeenetwork.com">get Free Advice</a> for all businesses
affected by the regulations.</p>
]]></description>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2007 16:50:26 +0100</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="true">/news/2007/05/20/donate-unwanted-pcs/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Leigh Scott</dc:creator>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Running for Charity</title>
		<link>/news/2007/05/08/running-for-charity/</link>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The <a href="http://www.greatrun.org">2007 BUPA Great North Run</a> will take place on Sunday 30th September 2007,
it&#8217;s 27th anniversary, and promises to be a day to remember! It&#8217;s the world&#8217;s biggest half marathon, a
point-to-point 13.1 mile course starting in Newcastle and finishing in South Shields. Over 50,000 runners lined up at the
start last year - with hundreds more people watching it from the sidelines and coverage on the BBC.</p>

<p>Luckily, I have managed to get through the selection process to take part in the event this year. This will be my third
half marathon. At the moment I have done two, <a href="http://www.staffordbc.gov.uk/static/page1784.htm">The Stafford Half
Marathon in 2006</a> and in 2007.</p>

<p>I won&#8217;t be breaking any <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Half_marathon">half marathon records</a>, but will be
raising money for my preferred charities, <a href="http://www.donnalouisetrust.org">The Donna Louise Trust</a> and the <a
href="https://www.nspcc.org.uk">NSPCC</a>. As you can guess I am looking for sponsorship to help out these two very worthy
causes. Any amount no matter how small will go to help unfortunate children.</p>

<p>The run is going to be televised so perhaps you would like me to wear something branded with your company logo for a
donation. A t-shirt, cap, badge, stickers, flag or anything else you may suggest. I may even wear a stupid costume if the
donation is high enough. I will have to draw the line at high heels though and save that sort of thing for my private
weekend activities.</p>

<p>If you would like to help with a donation <a href="mailto:leigh@creation.uk.com">drop me an email</a> or give me a call
at the office on 01785 716136. Thanks Leigh.</p>
]]></description>
		<pubDate>Tue,  8 May 2007 11:35:07 +0100</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="true">/news/2007/05/08/running-for-charity/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Leigh Scott</dc:creator>
	</item>
</channel>
</rss>
