<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:html="http://www.w3.org/TR/REC-html40" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
<channel>
<title>Creation: Latest Articles with the Tag "Leigh Scott" (RSS)</title>
<link>https://creation.trovster.com</link>
<description>Creation: Latest Articles with the Tag "Leigh Scott" (RSS)</description>
<link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://creation.trovster.com/" />
<link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://creation.trovster.com/archives/leigh-scott/rss/" />
<language>en</language>
<ttl>300</ttl>
	<item>
		<title>Running for Charity</title>
		<link>https://creation.trovster.com/news/2007/05/08/running-for-charity/</link>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>The <a href="http://www.greatrun.org">2007 BUPA Great North Run</a> will take place on Sunday 30th September 2007,
it&#8217;s 27th anniversary, and promises to be a day to remember! It&#8217;s the world&#8217;s biggest half marathon, a
point-to-point 13.1 mile course starting in Newcastle and finishing in South Shields. Over 50,000 runners lined up at the
start last year - with hundreds more people watching it from the sidelines and coverage on the BBC.</p>

<p>Luckily, I have managed to get through the selection process to take part in the event this year. This will be my third
half marathon. At the moment I have done two, <a href="http://www.staffordbc.gov.uk/static/page1784.htm">The Stafford Half
Marathon in 2006</a> and in 2007.</p>

<p>I won&#8217;t be breaking any <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Half_marathon">half marathon records</a>, but will be
raising money for my preferred charities, <a href="http://www.donnalouisetrust.org">The Donna Louise Trust</a> and the <a
href="https://www.nspcc.org.uk">NSPCC</a>. As you can guess I am looking for sponsorship to help out these two very worthy
causes. Any amount no matter how small will go to help unfortunate children.</p>

<p>The run is going to be televised so perhaps you would like me to wear something branded with your company logo for a
donation. A t-shirt, cap, badge, stickers, flag or anything else you may suggest. I may even wear a stupid costume if the
donation is high enough. I will have to draw the line at high heels though and save that sort of thing for my private
weekend activities.</p>

<p>If you would like to help with a donation <a href="mailto:leigh@creation.uk.com">drop me an email</a> or give me a call
at the office on 01785 716136. Thanks Leigh.</p>
]]></description>
		<pubDate>Tue,  8 May 2007 11:35:07 +0100</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="true">https://creation.trovster.com/news/2007/05/08/running-for-charity/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Leigh Scott</dc:creator>
	</item>
</channel>
</rss>
