<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:html="http://www.w3.org/TR/REC-html40" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
<channel>
<title>Creation: Latest Articles with the Tag "Computers" (RSS)</title>
<link>https://creation.trovster.com</link>
<description>Creation: Latest Articles with the Tag "Computers" (RSS)</description>
<link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://creation.trovster.com/" />
<link rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="https://creation.trovster.com/archives/computers/rss/" />
<language>en</language>
<ttl>300</ttl>
	<item>
		<title>Donate Unwanted PCs</title>
		<link>https://creation.trovster.com/news/2007/05/20/donate-unwanted-pcs/</link>
		<description><![CDATA[<p>Help students in The Gambia with your unwanted PCs. Following a visit to the region by our good friends at <a
href="http://www.tlc.ac.uk">Tamworth &amp; Lichfield College</a>, John Fontaine and Belinda Ball, we are trying to help them
collect computer equipment for students to use in Gambia.</p>

<p>This part of the world is very poor but everyone is keen to learn. The students have very limited facilities at present
and in some cases are using very old manual typewriters to learn keyboard skills. So our unwanted PCs would be a distinct
step up for them.</p>

<p>John and a friend of the College have made arrangements to ship any working PCs, capable of running Windows 2000, to the
College in The Gambia. A container will be packed up and sent over when it&#8217;s full. <a
href="mailto:leigh@creation.uk.com">Let me know</a> if you have any PCs you would like to donate.</p>

<p>You could also be saving money by helping out, now the Regulations implementing the <a
href="http://www.netregs.gov.uk/netregs/legislation/380525/473094/?lang=_e">WEEE Directive</a> (Waste Electrical and
Electronic Equipment) in the UK were entered into force on 2nd January 2007. A directive to promote recycling and reduce
waste. Find out more about the WEEE Directive and <a href="http://weeenetwork.com">get Free Advice</a> for all businesses
affected by the regulations.</p>
]]></description>
		<pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2007 16:50:26 +0100</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="true">https://creation.trovster.com/news/2007/05/20/donate-unwanted-pcs/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Leigh Scott</dc:creator>
	</item>
</channel>
</rss>
